budgetvm.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

BudgetVM has a long-standing policy of protecting customer privacy.

We believe that you should know what information we collect from you, as well as how that information is used, disclosed, and protected. We have created this policy statement (the "Policy") to explain our privacy practices and policies.

We will not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this Policy or our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy. We may use information about who you are, where and when you browse on the Web, where your wireless device is located, and how you use our network to provide you better service and enrich your user experience when you sign up or use any of our products or services.

The BudgetVM website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. To opt-out of receiving targeted advertising please visit www.aboutads.info or the NAI opt-out site at networkadvertising.org/choices, or for those in Europe, the EDAA opt out site at youronlinechoices.eu.

BudgetVM may make available shorter or machine-readable versions of this Privacy Policy. These additional policies are intended only as summaries of this complete Privacy Policy. This Policy applies to customers who purchase and use our services and products in the United States. Collection, use, disclosure, and protection of personal information may be subject to different regulation outside the United States.

BudgetVM will revise and update this Policy as it deems appropriate, including, for example, if our practices change or if changes in the law so require. You should refer back to this page for the latest information.
